<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Gatsby Starter Blog RSS Feed]]></title><description><![CDATA[About Gabin]]></description><link>https://agb94.github.io</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 08:08:09 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[🙋‍♀️ Life update]]></title><description><![CDATA[It’s hard to believe my last blog post was in 2023. The AutoFL work I mentioned back then was (thankfully?) accepted to FSE’24, and…]]></description><link>https://agb94.github.io/update/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://agb94.github.io/update/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;It’s hard to believe my last blog post was in 2023. The AutoFL work I mentioned back then was (thankfully?) accepted to FSE’24, and somewhere along the way it passed 100 citations on Google Scholar. A lot has happened since then, so here’s a quick roundup of the biggest changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://coinse.github.io/2024/06/04/Gabin-PhD.html&quot;&gt;I completed my PhD in August 2024&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A long journey finally came to an end. Finishing it felt both relieving and bittersweet, and I’m grateful for all the people who supported me along the way. And.. I still miss COINSE!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&quot;2&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I started a new job at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.roku.com/&quot;&gt;Roku&lt;/a&gt; Seoul Office in June 2024&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I met lots of amazing people there, and the industry experience taught me a lot, and many of those lessons continue to help even now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol start=&quot;3&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Since September 2025, I’ve been an &lt;a href=&quot;https://ku-selene.github.io/&quot;&gt;Assistant Professor at Korea University&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was a big decision I’d been contemplating for years, and I’m glad I made the leap back into academia. Being able to do research again (and teaching!) has been deeply satisfying.
Advising students has been refreshing and genuinely fun. I’m also thankful for everyone around me who has been incredibly supportive during this transition. 🥺&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;These days, I had been working on multiple topics including &lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/2510.22530&quot;&gt;AutoCrashFL&lt;/a&gt; (essentially taking AutoFL ideas into real industrial crash debugging) and also exploring a few new research directions I’m excited about. I’m curious to see what kinds of work will come out over the next several years.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also attended &lt;a href=&quot;https://conf.researchr.org/home/ase-2025&quot;&gt;ASE’25&lt;/a&gt; in Seoul this year, my first in-person conference in a while. As a publicity co-chair, I was also the one behind the &lt;a href=&quot;https://bsky.app/profile/aseconf.bsky.social&quot;&gt;ASE’25 Bluesky account&lt;/a&gt; 😏 The SE community feels very different in the post-LLM era. It’s exciting to see people tackling problems that used to be nearly impossible, but at the same time, the uniqueness of techniques feels (a bit) reduced, making it almost like a puzzle to identify what the actual contribution is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All in all, it has been a period full of change, both personally and academically.
Maybe the next blog post will be in 2027… but hopefully I’ll have good news to share when it comes.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AutoFL: LLM-Based Fault Localization]]></title><description><![CDATA[My colleague Sungmin and I have been collaborating on using language models 🤖 for automated fault localization (FL). Our approach, called…]]></description><link>https://agb94.github.io/autofl/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://agb94.github.io/autofl/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;My colleague Sungmin and I have been collaborating on using language models 🤖 for automated fault localization (FL).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our approach, called &lt;strong&gt;AutoFL&lt;/strong&gt;, allows the language model to autonomously retrieve necessary information for fault localization, using provided details about failures. This process is analogous to how human developers utilize different sources of information while debugging.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span
      class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-wrapper&quot;
      style=&quot;position: relative; display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; max-width: 601px; &quot;
    &gt;
      &lt;a
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-link&quot;
    href=&quot;/static/262aa8429abdb05dfd91945e9ca09c6c/d8f62/autofl_overview.png&quot;
    style=&quot;display: block&quot;
    target=&quot;_blank&quot;
    rel=&quot;noopener&quot;
  &gt;
    &lt;span
    class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-background-image&quot;
    style=&quot;padding-bottom: 46.202531645569614%; position: relative; bottom: 0; left: 0; background-image: url(&apos;data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABQAAAAJCAYAAAAywQxIAAAACXBIWXMAAAsTAAALEwEAmpwYAAAB7klEQVQoz22Q624ScRDF9418Dl/JD218AT/1izFRkya92FpaWG5thUWKuOwqpUvKbblTYLkuUCCQ0J/5/23VqJNMZnJmzpmTUSqVCul0mnqtSqNq404mrFYrlssli8WC9XpNu91G0zSazeav2dP84eFB4pFIhG63i5LNZjEMk1wuRzaToVQqkc/ncRyHTqcjxXq9HqPRSFaBCWKr1ULXdYkNh0Ourq6ksCKIAug6Ds5wiDggFu/v7+n3+1JIzAeDgazD0Uhi4/GYeDwuDxaLRfZ2d7FublAsy8LvU/lipjhLaNTrdelWLAmicHJ3d0f30W3nMUVfLpdxXZfxZEK2WsedL1Cm06kEZ7MZY3csfzKfzxGHlqsVVcviWzDEZ88puj9AUlVJBQIkvD7ysRjlUolRs0b5zSscI4HCf6JQKKBFozTbbRqZa4wPhySPDvl+esLXo0My3jPMk2PyARW7UCR7GST1/Bn2+x0U4ejPFLHZbOTja/UaGeMazR9FPfJx6b0g7AnJeu4JoX9KYhdt3EEf3+sdbg39t8O/hYXoajknZVVRExXeHkc4CBjsqTrvPmrs+1NcmC2snI1pGrzYfok/GPxX8Kn/2WwwMzbx6w6esMGxP4knbHLgjRNNVYmZDW4LFWy7xPbWFufhMD8AoDSBOuo6V9kAAAAASUVORK5CYII=&apos;); background-size: cover; display: block;&quot;
  &gt;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;img
        class=&quot;gatsby-resp-image-image&quot;
        alt=&quot;AutoFL Overview&quot;
        title=&quot;AutoFL Overview&quot;
        src=&quot;/static/262aa8429abdb05dfd91945e9ca09c6c/d8f62/autofl_overview.png&quot;
        srcset=&quot;/static/262aa8429abdb05dfd91945e9ca09c6c/c26ae/autofl_overview.png 158w,
/static/262aa8429abdb05dfd91945e9ca09c6c/6bdcf/autofl_overview.png 315w,
/static/262aa8429abdb05dfd91945e9ca09c6c/d8f62/autofl_overview.png 601w&quot;
        sizes=&quot;(max-width: 601px) 100vw, 601px&quot;
        style=&quot;width:100%;height:100%;margin:0;vertical-align:middle;position:absolute;top:0;left:0;&quot;
        loading=&quot;lazy&quot;
        decoding=&quot;async&quot;
      /&gt;
  &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;AutoFL provides a prompt to the LLM containing failing test information and descriptions of available functions for debugging to LLM (Input: &lt;strong&gt;Failure Symptom, Test Code&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The LLM interacts with the provided functions autonomously, to extract the information needed for the debugging of the given failure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Based on the gathered information, the LLM generates an explanation about the root cause of the observed failure. (Output: &lt;strong&gt;Root Cause Explanation&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The user queries for the location of the identified bug&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The LLM responds by providing the culprit method. (Output: &lt;strong&gt;Buggy Location&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our initial evaluation has yielded promising results: when provided with a single failing test information and a set of basic functions for coverage retrieval and code navigation, AutoFL outperforms Spectrum-Based FL in terms of the number of perfect predictions. Feel free to check out our preprint for more details (&lt;a href=&quot;https://arxiv.org/abs/2308.05487&quot;&gt;https://arxiv.org/abs/2308.05487&lt;/a&gt;), and don’t hesitate to reach out if you have any questions!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[[ICSE'23] Fonte: Finding Bug Inducing Commits from Failures]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am thrilled to share the exciting news that our paper titled “Fonte: Finding Bug Inducing Commits from Failures” has been accepted at ICSE…]]></description><link>https://agb94.github.io/fonte/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://agb94.github.io/fonte/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I am thrilled to share the exciting news that our paper titled &lt;a href=&quot;https://coinse.github.io/publications/pdfs/An2023aa.pdf&quot;&gt;“Fonte: Finding Bug Inducing Commits from Failures”&lt;/a&gt; has been accepted at ICSE 2023. This work builds upon our previous research on &lt;a href=&quot;https://coinse.github.io/publications/pdfs/An2021qb.pdf&quot;&gt;Reducing the Search Space of Bug Inducing Commits (BICs) Using Failure Coverage&lt;/a&gt;, where we proposed a technique to narrow down the search space for bug-inducing commits using the coverage of failing executions. In this latest paper, we introduce a novel method, named Fonte, for quantifying the suspiciousness of commits, moving beyond mere search space reduction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fonte is founded on a unique combination of Fault Localization (FL) and commit history mining. The core idea behind our approach is that&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A commit is more likely to be a BIC if it introduced or modified code that is relevant to a particular failure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To measure the relevance of code elements to the observed failure, we employ Fault Localization techniques. We then devise a voting system wherein each code element “votes” for the commits that introduced or modified it. The voting power of a code element is determined by its FL ranking, with a decay factor applied to older commits. This decay factor stems from our hypothesis that older commits are less likely to be responsible for the current failure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our evaluation demonstrates that Fonte is highly effective in identifying bug-inducing commits based on fault localization scores and exhibits superior performance compared to IR-based BIC identification techniques. The detailed results and findings can be found in our paper!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[[ISSTA'22] FDG: A Precise Measurement of Fault Diagnosability Gain of Test Cases]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am delighted to announce that our paper titled “FDG: A Precise Measurement of Fault Diagnosability Gain of Test Cases” has been accepted…]]></description><link>https://agb94.github.io/fdg/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://agb94.github.io/fdg/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I am delighted to announce that our paper titled &lt;a href=&quot;https://coinse.github.io/publications/pdfs/An2022pb.pdf&quot;&gt;“FDG: A Precise Measurement of Fault Diagnosability Gain of Test Cases”&lt;/a&gt; has been accepted at ACM SIGSOFT International Symposium on Software Testing and Analysis (ISSTA 2022)! This work proposes a novel measure FDG to quantify the fault diagnosability gain of individual test cases. Using the test coverage and the ongoing Fault Localisation (FL) results, FDG can precisely measure how much diagnosability gain each test can bring to the current test suite i.e., the fault-finding capability of a test case.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;FDG help developers and testers to prioritize the most effective test cases for enhancing the test suite. This is especially helpful in the following fault localization scenarios:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Iterative Fault Localization: When the current test suite’s fault diagnosability is low, and traditional SBFL (Spectrum-Based Fault Localization) techniques are not yielding satisfactory results, additional test cases can be generated using automated test generation tools. In that case, whether each of the auto-gen test cases is revealing the fault or not (= oracle problem) should be checked by developers or testers before they are used for fault localization. However, manually inspecting all the generated test cases can be time-consuming and impractical. In this situation, FDG can help prioritize the most valuable auto-generated test cases that are expected to improve the FL accuracy the most, thus saving valuable developer time.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Selective Test Case Addition: During regression testing, a subset of test cases is often selected to minimize test execution costs while maintaining fault detection ability. However, when test failures occur, it may be necessary to add not-executed test cases to improve fault localization accuracy. FDG can aid in this process by using past coverage information of not-executed test cases as a proxy for their actual coverage and selecting the most promising test cases within a given budget.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m excited about sharing our findings at the conference and look forward to discussing our work with the SE community!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[[ICSE'22] Automatically Identifying Shared Root Causes of Test Breakages in SAP HANA]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m excited to share that our paper titled “Automatically Identifying Shared Root Causes of Test Breakages in SAP HANA” has been accepted…]]></description><link>https://agb94.github.io/sap_failure_clustering/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://agb94.github.io/sap_failure_clustering/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2022 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;I’m excited to share that our paper titled &lt;a href=&quot;https://coinse.github.io/publications/pdfs/An2022qe.pdf&quot;&gt;“Automatically Identifying Shared Root Causes of Test Breakages in SAP HANA”&lt;/a&gt; has been accepted for presentation in the &lt;strong&gt;Software Engineering In Practice&lt;/strong&gt; track at the 44th IEEE/ACM International Conference on Software Engineering (ICSE 2022). This collaborative work, conducted in partnership with COINSE and SAP Labs Korea 😉, focuses on identifying the shared root causes among test failures. By accurately measuring the test failure similarity, we can group similar failures together when presenting them to developers and prevent an overwhelming number of bug reports. The study involves evaluating and comparing these similarity metrics using CI data from SAP HANA, a commercial database system. The investigation reveals that various information sources, such as static, dynamic, and historical data, complement each other, with the dynamic similarity metric performing best. I really look forward to presenting our work at ICSE 2022!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[New Beginnings]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is my first post on this new blog. How exciting! 😋 To make this blog, I used Gatsby.
It is pretty easy to make a website with Gatsby…]]></description><link>https://agb94.github.io/new_beginnings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://agb94.github.io/new_beginnings/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 13:40:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This is my first post on this new blog. How exciting! 😋&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To make this blog, I used &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gatsbyjs.com/&quot;&gt;Gatsby&lt;/a&gt;.
It is pretty easy to make a website with Gatsby because there are plenty of
great starter packs. I used one of the most popular themes:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/gatsbyjs/gatsby-starter-blog&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;gatsby-starter-blog&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Brief Tutorial: How to make a blog with Gatsby&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prerequisite: &lt;a href=&quot;https://nodejs.org/en/&quot;&gt;Node.js&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;1. Enable &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/nodejs/corepack&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;corepack&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Corepack is a zero-runtime-dependency Node.js script that comes
with the installation of Node.js.
If you enable corepack, you can use &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;Yarn&lt;/code&gt;, a JavaScript package manager.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;shell&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;language-shell&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-shell&quot;&gt;corepack &lt;span class=&quot;token builtin class-name&quot;&gt;enable&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;2. Install &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;gatsby-cli&lt;/code&gt; using &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;yarn&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;shell&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;language-shell&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-shell&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token function&quot;&gt;yarn&lt;/span&gt; global &lt;span class=&quot;token function&quot;&gt;add&lt;/span&gt; gatsby-cli&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;3. Create a new project with a pre-made template.&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;shell&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;language-shell&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-shell&quot;&gt;gatsby new &lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;your-blog-name&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;&gt;&lt;/span&gt; https://github.com/gatsbyjs/gatsby-starter-blog
&lt;span class=&quot;token builtin class-name&quot;&gt;cd&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;your-blog-name&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
gatsby develop &lt;span class=&quot;token comment&quot;&gt;# run the development server&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can now check out your blog at &lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:8000/&quot;&gt;http://localhost:8000/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;4. Customize your website&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have no clue?
Here are &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/agb94/agb94.github.io/tree/develop&quot;&gt;the changes&lt;/a&gt; that I made to this website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;5. Deploy your website with GitHub Pages&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First, you need to create a new repository on GitHub.
The repository name should be &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;your-github-id&gt;.github.io&lt;/code&gt; (this will be the url for your website).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;shell&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;language-shell&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-shell&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token function&quot;&gt;git&lt;/span&gt; init &lt;span class=&quot;token builtin class-name&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;token function&quot;&gt;git&lt;/span&gt; remote &lt;span class=&quot;token function&quot;&gt;add&lt;/span&gt; origin https://github.com/&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;your-github-id&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;/&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;your-github-id&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.github.io
&lt;span class=&quot;token function&quot;&gt;npm&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;token function&quot;&gt;install&lt;/span&gt; gh-pages --save-dev&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Next, add the deploy command &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;gatsby build &amp;amp;&amp;amp; gh-pages -d public -b main&lt;/code&gt; to &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;package.json&lt;/code&gt;.
You can use any branch name other than &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;main&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;json&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;language-json&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-json&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token property&quot;&gt;&quot;scripts&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;token property&quot;&gt;&quot;build&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;token string&quot;&gt;&quot;gatsby build&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;token property&quot;&gt;&quot;develop&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;token string&quot;&gt;&quot;gatsby develop&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;token property&quot;&gt;&quot;deploy&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;token string&quot;&gt;&quot;gatsby build &amp;amp;&amp;amp; gh-pages -d public -b main&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; # add this!
    &lt;span class=&quot;token property&quot;&gt;&quot;format&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;token string&quot;&gt;&quot;prettier --write \&quot;**/*.{js,jsx,ts,tsx,json,md}\&quot;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;token property&quot;&gt;&quot;start&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;token string&quot;&gt;&quot;gatsby develop&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;token property&quot;&gt;&quot;serve&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;token string&quot;&gt;&quot;gatsby serve&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;token property&quot;&gt;&quot;clean&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;token string&quot;&gt;&quot;gatsby clean&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;span class=&quot;token property&quot;&gt;&quot;test&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;token string&quot;&gt;&quot;echo \&quot;Write tests! -&gt; https://gatsby.dev/unit-testing\&quot; &amp;amp;&amp;amp; exit 1&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, this command will automatically deploy your blog to GitHub Pages with
GitHub actions. This may take up a few minutes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;shell&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;language-shell&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-shell&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token function&quot;&gt;npm&lt;/span&gt; run deploy&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>